# **Jackson Collins**

# jacksoncofficial3@gmail.com

21404 Santa Rosa Ave.

(601)-407-8652

An incoming freshman to the Unversity of Texas at San Antonio, majoring in computer science with a minor in cyber security. Having been passionate about programming from a farily young age, Jackson has good experience with programming in many paradigms and tech stacks. With an enthusiasm for research, especially in machine learning, making computers solve problems is Jackson's mission.

# **Professional History**

## Institute for Computing in Research - Internship

2024-07-08 - 2024-08-03

Intern to Cole Agard, working on the Blacklight library. Blacklight is a project aiming to use genetic algorithms to create topologically optimized neural networks.

#### Education

#### Mini-lessons

2024-02-08 - Ongoing

Biweekly lessons taught by Mark Galassi teaching a variety of computer science and math topics including, fitting functions to datasets, Fourier analysis, memory, agent based modeling and cryptography.

## **Python Course**

2024-01-27

Class taught by Mark Galassi that teaches the fundementals of the Python programming language

## Lago Vista High School

2020-2024

- AP Computer Science score of 4
- OnRamps<sup>1</sup> Algebra 2
- OnRamps PreCal
- OnRamps Statistics
- AP Calculus AB
- Theatre Tech

### Skills

- · Ability to quickly pick up new languages and tech stacks
- Python
- Java
- Go
- Javascript
- PyTorch

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>1</sup>UT Austin class and material taught by High School teacher